Hon, I'm glad
Dex got out of the hospital already.
I'm so happy to finally see you.
Hey! Why are you hugging my wife?
Who are you?
That's our house!
Why are you in our house?
- Where's my wife?
- Punch him!
Where's Joyce?
Where's Dex? What's going on?
Maybe you need to sober up first.
Get him inside until he sobers up.
Wait, wait... Sir! Sir! Sir!
Kid, you can come out now.
Liam, son.
There wasn't a day
that I didn't wish to be with you.
I will wake up.
I will wake up from this nightmare!
What the...
Hello, Love.
We met seven years ago.
On a bridge near the bus stop
in a province far from Manila.
It was that fateful day when...
I thought I was all alone.
Then you came into my life.
Then from then on, we became inseparable.
When was it again?
March 22, 2015.
At a bus stop?
In a province far from Manila?
So instead of following Joyce that day,
I stayed inside the bus
and reached the last bus stop.
And that's where I met this woman?
Is no one else getting off?
Next stop, Segunda!
Get in.
Is there anyone else going to Segunda?
Boss.
[Segunda Bus Stop]
Make sure everyone gets off.
That's why...
every March 22, we celebrate our meetsary.
It matters to us more than our anniversary.
Because you changed my life...
by just being there for me.
Liam.
I want you to know...
I'm willing to do that to you, too.
I am here for you
whatever you are going through.
You can tell me anything.
I'll be the last person to judge you.
I don't understand what's happening.
I only tried to write down
everything that was on my mind.
I wished for my life to change.
I wished I wasn't the reason
for my wife and son's miserable life.
Then it was like magic...
When I woke up, I was here.
It was like a different world.
It's like this.
Same world, same universe.
But here, there are lots of new people.
I found out I was working
for my father's construction company.
I became wealthy.
I was able to pay for my mom's treatment.
And the plot twist here...
is that Joyce isn't part of my life.
I didn't marry the woman
I was supposed to marry.
But the ultimate plot twist is...
I met a different girl named Via.
They say she's my girlfriend.
She's not my wife yet.
We don't have a child...
We don't have a child together.
My son disappeared. Dex disappeared.
Well, in this dream of yours, Liam,
how will you describe what you felt,
realizing all the changes after you woke up?
Were you sad or happy?
It's not just a single emotion.
It's like I felt every emotion
all at the same time.
Confusion, sadness, happiness, excitement...
I felt it all at once, but...
But what's dominant is the question...
How could I do this?
How could I wish for it?
So there's guilt?
Maybe because there are wishes we only regret
once it comes true.
Well, it's a good thing
that everything's just a dream.
What I gather from your dream
is maybe you're having a midlife crisis.
You're having a hard time
appreciating the things you have.
Maybe you're looking for something new.
Maybe it's time for you
to develop a new career or a hobby,
like learning a foreign language,
or playing an instrument?
A change of career, perhaps.
Doc... Doc, sorry. Sorry.
Sir Liam, isn't your session done yet?
Sir Danilo has been calling me.
He's looking for you.
- One moment, Sir...
- What?
Let me fix your collar.
You're so formal.
Sorry, Sir, come again?
You're too formal with me.
This formal attire I'm wearing is enough.
You've been like that since the other day.
Good morning, Sir William Herrera.
And stop calling me "Sir".
Just call me Liam.
Good morning, Sir William!
[Casa Fuerte Properties]
I can't do that, Sir.
I don't want to lose my job.
You will lose your job
if you continue calling me "Sir".
I will fire you.
Please, don't do that, Si...
B-Boss Bro.
I'll just call you that.
I'm not going to fire you,
but Boss Bro is better.
Okay, as you wish, Boss Bro.
- Borj?
- What?
You've been working for me for years, right?
Six years and nine months to be exact.
Six years and nine months.
So that means you're already loyal to me?
I'm starting to get hurt
by your questions, Boss Bro.
I'm just checking.
I just want to ask for your opinion.
I talked to the psychiatrist.
She told me
maybe I needed a significant change
in my life.
Borj, if you're allowed
to go back to the past
to change or alter your life,
will you do it?
Just like in Miss Universe,
I would say no.
I'm standing here in front of you today
because of the things
that happened in my life.
May it be good or bad.
So, I won't change anything in my past.
That's all, and I thank you.
Borj, we're not in the Miss Universe pageant.
Of course, I would say yes.
There's always a part of our lives
that we regret.
So if I were given a chance
to change it, why not?
Right?
But our decisions will only lead us
to two directions.
It can bring us to the wrong path...
or to the right one.
And about the psychiatrist's advice
that something might be missing
in your life...
Well, I'll say there's none.
Because you already have everything.
You are the prince of
the Herrera Holdings Corporation,
especially here in Casa Fuerte.
Sir Liam!
Good morning.
Mister, hold on.
Borj, it's okay. Let him be. What is it?
I've been waiting for you, Sir.
Luckily, I'm on duty right now.
Mister, can you make it faster?
We're going to be late.
I will just give this food
that my wife cooked.
Sorry if this is the only thing
we can afford.
What's this?
That is a little token of appreciation...
for the help you've given us.
If it wasn't for you,
our youngest child wouldn't
get the treatment.
Is that so?
What is this?
Wow!
It's Ginataang Batute!
This is my favorite.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad to hear that, Sir.
I thought you do not eat food like that.
Thank you so much, Mister.
Please thank your wife,
and also say hi to your child for me.
Sir, we will be forever grateful to you.
Thank you so much, Sir.
I'll get going, Sir.
I'll go back to my duty now.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you so much too.
- Bye, Sir.
I'll get going. Please, excuse me.
Boss Bro, is that delicious?
My mom used to cook this.
Do you want to try it? We can share it.
Okay. I'm already hungry.
Come on, let's try it.
Okay, let's go.
This world is so different.
Who would have thought
that the man
who used to work himself to the ground
could now help others?
Boss Bro.
What's that? Do I need to read all that?
I've read all of it, Boss Bro.
You already approved everything.
You just need to sign.
I have to sign all of these?
But...
This one needs your approval.
Boss Bro, we don't have time
to go to the mall.
So they just sent these watches over,
since you're a valued customer
of their store.
All you need to do is choose.
Based on your taste,
this looks better, Boss Bro.
Hi, son.
Are you ready?
Ready for what, Dad?
Señor, you call him Señor here in the office.
Ready for what, Señor?
Come on.
Today is the groundbreaking ceremony.
Borj, you did not update your boss
about his schedule.
Sir Liam is ready, Señor.
Just a final touch.
Now he's ready, Señor.
Why are you here?
Aren't you busy in Blacksmith?
I have my men there, Dad.
They get paid, okay?
And besides, this is a big day
for my brother, right?
Groundbreaking ceremony.
The great Liam has again
surpassed his previous success.
Now, it's the biggest mall in Asia.
Wow!
You really are unstoppable, Bro.
I'll go get my boss, VLH.
If he gets injured,
he'll be less good-looking
when he gives his speech.
Speech?
[Grand Pacific Square:
The Biggest Mall in Asia]
Borj...
I didn't know I had to speak.
I thought you had it memorized
since last week.
That's how advanced you prepare.
I forgot about it, okay?
We're in trouble.
From being a small construction company,
we have evolved
into a giant development corporation.
All because of this guy over here.
So, it's just right
that he leads our biggest project.
Bigger than the biggest mall
in the continent.
It will be spearheaded by my son.
My son, William Herrera.
Hello.
The biggest mall in the biggest continent.
Lately, I've been bothered
by a huge question.
How prepared am I for this project?
The answer...
It's scary.
The pressure is scary.
It's scary when people go...
when people come.
But what's scarier...
are the things that change our lives.
Things that take us out of our comfort zone.
Things that we can't fully understand
at the beginning.
Just like accepting this project.
It's not just my life that's on the line.
The company and the country's image
are on the line, too.
But I realized...
a big change can be worthwhile.
And I just hope I can make you all proud
with this new project.
Because I'm no longer the man
who underestimates himself.
I am sorry to be the bearer of bad news.
But the network has decided
not to proceed with your concept.
And that decision has already been made.
I hope you are all proud of me.
Sir William, look here, please.
Liam!
Liam, son!
- Liam!
- Boss Bro.
Yes... your life changed.
And we were dragged into it!
You rose to the top...
While we die one by one.
You should die before anyone else!
You monster!
Dad, let's get out of here.
- What?
- He might not be alone.
- Please escort him out.
- Let's go.
- Please secure everything.
- Got it.
You are the reason why we're suffering!
Mister, who are you?
Why do you want to kill me?
Have you forgotten about it?
That's how you rich people are.
You treat poor people like cockroaches
that you can step on and eliminate!
Please get him out of here!
Something bad might happen to him.
I'm already old.
I've got nothing to lose.
Until my last breath...
I'll seek justice for what happened to us!
Sir, what happened?
Sir, why is that man furious at you?
Have you mistreated anyone?
We'll give a statement once we have
a full grasp of what happened here.
Wait, where are you taking the mister?
- Come on, son. Let's go home.
- Wait!
Mom, where are we going?
Home. Let's go home for now.
He's safer in the office, Ma'am Tess.
- Let's stay there for now.
- Come on. Let's go, son.
Liam, how are you? Are you okay?
"How are you", my foot!
You were the first to leave
when everything got crazy.
My God... I almost lost my son!
And the only thing you can say is,
"how are you"?
Mom...
If something happens to my son,
Danilo, I'm telling you.
You won't be able to handle me.
Ma'am Tess, it's a protocol
to first keep the CEO secured
during mishaps like the one earlier.
No, I can feel
that Danilo is doing something shady,
and my son is getting dragged into it.
Mom...
Oh, please, Tess.
Let me talk to my son first.
Oh, so he's your son now.
- But earlier, you...
- Mom, Mom, I'm okay.
It's okay. Dad, I'm okay.
I'm glad to hear that.
I had that old man investigated.
He needs to pay for what he did.
Are you going to send him to jail?
Of course!
He came with the intent to kill.
That's attempted murder.
But Dad, from what he said,
it looked like I was the one
who did them wrong.
What do you want to happen?
I want to know why he did that to me.
I want to talk to him.
Liam, I forbid you to do that.
He's probably not alone.
You can't get into trouble.
Tomorrow is the most important event
for our company,
for our company's future.
What's happening tomorrow?
Are you kidding me,
or are you trying to piss me off?
See? The truth finally comes out.
Right, Danilo?
Your work and your company
are more important to you.
Can't you be a father just this once, Danilo?
You and your mom should go home.
We better go home so you can get some rest.
You might get involved in
your father's illegal dealings.
Let's go.
Come on, Tess.
Are you blaming me for this, too?
Don't start with me, Danilo.
You won't be able to handle me.
That's enough.
Let's go.
I'll send security to watch over you.
Keep an eye on Liam.
He's stubborn.
He might leave to see that old man.
Go on.
Your father isn't useless after all.
Son, we're still not sure about your safety.
What's the important event
that you need to attend tomorrow?
Well, tomorrow we will have
the investors' conference
of Casa Fuerte Properties.
That's why the Señor said
that tomorrow's event is really important
for the future of our company.
To show investors
that Casa Fuerte is
on solid financial footing.
There are fears with the looming recession
that the real estate sector
will become vulnerable.
But since we are proceeding
with a mega development project,
this can definitely boost
investors' confidence.
Would you like some coffee?
I'll go to sleep now.
I've said a lot, but nobody seems to listen.
But you're right, Boss Bro.
Go to sleep
so you will be well-rested tomorrow.
But, Ma'am, can I charge my laptop here?
I'll just check Boss Bro's speech
for tomorrow.
Of course.
Go on, son. Go to bed now.
Get some rest.
Okay. Good night, Mom.
- Borj.
- Rest well, Boss Bro.
Ma'am, the... Ma'am, the coffee.
The coffee.
Oh, yeah.
- Coffee.
Yeah, for a while.
Wait here.
What's that?
Sorry, Mom.
I don't want you to worry.
With all of the things I don't understand
in this reality...
this one suddenly comes into the picture.
Is there any news about the identity
of the old man who attacked Liam?
My assistants are still finding out
who that elder is.
I'm still waiting for their reply.
I still haven't heard from Señor Danilo.
Your Señor? Oh, boy.
I don't trust him.
I'm sure he's hiding something.
He's the biggest swindler and liar I know.
Ma'am, speaking from experience?
What matters is that Liam is safe.
That man. I'm worried about him.
[National Police]
[Sto. Cristo Police District]
Chief...
Sir, why are you here?
Your father forbade you to come here.
That old man might not be alone.
You might get hurt.
Sir, don't worry about me.
I just want to talk to him.
Nestor!
Sir.
Now... I got your attention.
Mister...
I came here
to get a full grasp of everything.
Why did you do that to me?
I really can't remember anything.
Stop lying.
You can't fool us anymore.
I may be old,
but I don't forget the evil things you did,
especially you.
Mister, I'm telling the truth.
I really don't understand anything
from what you're saying.
You dazzled us with money
that turned out to be measly after all.
After you earned our trust,
you didn't keep your end of the bargain.
You tore down almost half of our neighborhood
and stole our means of living.
I won't let you fool and oppress us again!
That's the truth!
- Ma'am Tess.
- Yes?
Here, I got an e-mail.
Nestor Bartolome.
A resident of Verde Village.
The community
beside Casa Fuerte's Strongland Residences.
Strongland Residences...
Isn't that Liam's latest project?
Yes.
[Verde Village, Before]
[Verde Village, After]
I don't care if I rot in jail.
You have to pay for all your wrongdoings.
The law may be on your side,
but you will deal with the law of the poor.
Grandfather?
My grandchild.
Boss...
I'm begging you.
My grandfather is a good person.
He only did that
because of his love
for us and the people of Verde Village.
That's why...
Boss, I'm begging you.
Let my grandfather go.
You can put me in jail instead.
Put me in jail instead of him.
Please. He's old.
Something bad might happen to him.
Put me in jail instead.
If you need to lock someone up, let it be me.
Boss, please.
I will do everything.
If you really need to lock someone up,
let it be me.
Let my grandfather go.
You have to leave, Sir.
We don't want you to get in trouble.
Boss.
My grandchild.
Liam.
Mom.
What has gotten into your head
that you came here?
I came to understand everything.
But I only got more confused.
Boss Bro...
we already know why he ran amok.
Son.
Don't be impulsive.
It's good I know
what's running through your head.
I knew you were going to see that old man.
Sorry, Mom.
Mister Nestor told me
that I spoke with the residents.
That's something you should remember
because you are...
But Boss Bro...
you meet a lot of people every day.
So it's possible that you won't remember him,
especially if you're focused on the project.
But why are they furious at me?
What did I do wrong?
Son, only Danilo can answer our questions.
Do you want me to talk to your dad?
Hold on.
Oh, son.
He sent a message.
Danilo is in our house.
The security already reported to him
that you went out.
Mom, I don't want to see Dad
after what I discovered tonight.
He might dictate again
how I should handle things.
Where will we go, son?
[Incoming call: Dad]
What more plot twists should I expect?
Universe, take it easy.
I'm glad you came here, Auntie.
I told Liam that it might not be a good idea,
because it's already late.
It's all right with me, Auntie.
Love, I'm so sorry.
I got so busy with work today.
I wasn't able to check on you.
Are you really okay?
Are you hurt? Did you get yourself checked?
I'm okay, Via.
I don't want you to worry about my troubles.
Don't worry about you?
Love, I'm your girlfriend.
I worry the same way your mom does.
Son, you're being impulsive.
Mom.
Where can I take a nap, Via?
You can use the guest room, Auntie.
- Over there?
- Yes.
- Do you need help?
- No. Thank you.
When you're stressed...
this is the only thing
that makes you feel better.
Aren't you turned off?
You learned how ruthless I am
when it comes to business.
No.
One thing I know about you...
is that when you do something bad,
you do it for a good reason.
Liam, you taught me
that everyone can have a second chance.
Just like how you gave me
my second chance at happiness.
Thank you...
for still believing in me.
[Annual Investors Conference]
Everyone, a warm applause
to the man of the hour.
Our special guest...
is the great and hard-working congressman,
Ramon dela Peña.
Congressman, thank you very much
for gracing this occasion
despite your very busy schedule.
- Thank you, Sir.
- Thank you, thank you.
With him is his beautiful daughter,
Victoria dela Peña.
- Thank you, Danilo.
- Thank you, thank you.
This is the engineer.
Oh, engineer...
- Love.
- Thank you...
This is Engineer Diaz.
Sorry I did not tell you I was coming.
Dad suddenly asked me to come.
It's okay.
Boss Bro...
I know lots of things
have been bothering you.
So here.
Just read it so we can be over and done with,
with the conference.
Do the right thing.
- Thank you, Danilo.
- Thank you.
Engineer Diaz, nice to meet you.
We'll talk later.
Sure, Dad...
Right after my speech.
Who said you are going to speak?
I'll take care of it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let us all give a warm welcome
to the man that we all call "Señor".
Oh...
Well, I guess
there has been some slight changes
to the program.
So, ladies and gentlemen,
let us begin this conference.
Engineer William Herrera.
Thank you so much for that warm welcome.
To my dad, the president of Herrera Group,
Señor Danilo Herrera.
To the Board of Directors...
and to all of you here
who share the vision of our organization...
Welcome to this year's investors' conference.
What is your son doing?
I don't know, my friend.
Let me begin by telling you...
how exciting this year is for all of us.
A big change is coming for everyone.
Hey Nestor,
looks like the man you wanted to stab
has a big company event.
Through the years,
we have overlooked our values
as an organization.
And that's wrong.
Ours is not a perfect company,
but that doesn't mean
we won't do things for the greater good.
It's not just for our own sake,
but also for the lives of every community
we are supposed to serve.
Because of our desire to make money,
we forget about how to be human.
And I don't think
that is the sustainable way
to run this business.
So tonight, I announce...
that I will put on hold
all the development projects of Casa Fuerte
for the time being.
And I will hire an independent firm
to assess the environmental impact
and effects of our projects.
I think it's only right
that we take it to heart
the real meaning of property development.
Turn the mic off.
A company that doesn't trample on anyone.
A company that doesn't hurt anyone.
I know that a lot of you will disagree.
There will be setbacks.
But I promise you,
that we will become a better company.
Let's get out of here.
What was that about?
I'm just doing the right thing, Dad.
Do you suddenly feel guilt?
When will you do the right thing?
Do you think I am the one
who calls the shots in Casa Fuerte?
Are you not?
I thought this is a chance
for us to get along.
But what have you done?
You turned me into the bad guy!
Are you a fool?
Did you hit your head somewhere?
Have you forgotten?
Everything we do in Casa Fuerte is your idea!
We are successful because of you.
I may love money, but you are greedy!
That's a lie!
None of what you said is true!
Liam!
[Antique Typewriter for sale]
[Second-hand sale]
[Online Shop for secondhand items]
Son...
[Trade-ins.net, Typewriters]
Time to eat.
My son...
Liam...
I went to your office,
but they said you weren't there.
I need an update
on the environmental clearances I asked for.
Didn't you hear me?
No one is taking care of the clearances.
It's business as usual again in Casa Fuerte.
None of the investors and directors
believe in your vision.
What do you mean?
What's so difficult to understand
in what I said?
You revealed everything
that's happening in Casa Fuerte
because of what you did at the conference.
So, as of today...
you're no longer the president of Casa Fuerte.
I can do it, Dad.
I can make us better.
We don't need to become evil.
I said, you're done with Casa Fuerte!
You've done enough damage!
We do unthinkable things
because of intense feelings of love.
You tore down
almost half of our neighborhood.
And you stole our livelihood.
Please, don't throw my grandfather
behind bars.
Lock me up instead.
Let it be me.
Mom...
You taught me
that everyone deserves a second chance.
This time...
showing your weakness is not cowardice.
I thought everything would be better
if you were here.
So, I'm giving you a second chance, Liam.
Are you putting me back to Casa Fuerte?
No. But I will put you in another company.
In Blacksmith Productions.
Isn't that Vergil's production house?
Who would have thought?
Casa Fuerte's wonder boy,
Herrera's prodigal son,
ended up in my company.
Of all people who look at that billboard,
you're the only one who's sad.
Well, maybe that's how it goes. Right, Bro?
She's up there and you're down here.
Is everything set?
Have you checked everything?
Yes, Miss Via.
Our vlog interview for today
is just a mini challenge.
Speaking of, our guest is already here.